export default {
  id: 'low_1006_2_1b',
  name: '상용한자(2학년-1/한자찾기)',
  data: [
    { question: '독:ひがし/음:とう', answer: ['東'] },
    { question: '독:にし/음:せい、さい', answer: ['西'] },
    { question: '독:みなみ/음:なん、[な]', answer: ['南'] },
    { question: '독:きた/음:ほく', answer: ['北'] },
    { question: '독:はる/음:しゅん', answer: ['春'] },
    { question: '독:なつ/음:か、[げ]', answer: ['夏'] },
    { question: '독:あき/음:しゅう', answer: ['秋'] },
    { question: '독:ふゆ/음:とう', answer: ['冬'] },
    { question: '독:ちち/음:ふ', answer: ['父'] },
    { question: '독:はは/음:ぼ', answer: ['母'] },
    { question: '독:あに/음:けい、[きょう]', answer: ['兄'] },
    { question: '독:おとうと/음:てい、[だい]、[で]', answer: ['弟'] },
    { question: '독:あね/음:し', answer: ['姉'] },
    { question: '독:いもうと/음:まい', answer: ['妹'] },
    { question: '독:おや、した(しい)、した(しむ)/음:しん', answer: ['親'] },
    { question: '독:とも/음:ゆう', answer: ['友'] },
    { question: '독:みずか(ら)/음:じ、し', answer: ['自'] },
    { question: '독:わ(ける)、わ(かれる)、わ(かる)、わ(かつ)/음:ぶん、ふん、ぶ', answer: ['分'] },
    { question: '독:ふる(い)、ふる(す)/음:こ', answer: ['古'] },
    { question: '독:いま/음:こん、きん', answer: ['今'] },
    { question: '독:うち/음:ない、[だい]', answer: ['内'] },
    { question: '독:そと、ほか、はず(す)、はず(れる)/음:がい、げ', answer: ['外'] },
    { question: '독:まえ/음:ぜん', answer: ['前'] },
    { question: '독:のち、うし(ろ)、あと、おく(れる)/음:ご、こう', answer: ['後'] },
    { question: '독:おお(い)/음:た', answer: ['多'] },
    { question: '독:すく(ない)、すこ(し)/음:しょう', answer: ['少'] },
    { question: '독:つよ(い)、つよ(まる)、つよ(める)、し(いる)/음:きょう、ごう', answer: ['強'] },
    { question: '독:よわ(い)、よわ(る)、よわ(まる)、よわ(める)/음:じゃく', answer: ['弱'] },
    { question: '독:とお(い)/음:えん、[おん]', answer: ['遠'] },
    { question: '독:ちか(い)/음:きん', answer: ['近'] },
    { question: '독:일만/음:まん、ばん', answer: ['万'] },
    { question: '독:うし/음:ぎゅう', answer: ['牛'] },
    { question: '독:うま、ま/음:ば', answer: ['馬'] },
    { question: '독:さかな、うお/음:ぎょ', answer: ['魚'] },
    { question: '독:とり/음:ちょう', answer: ['鳥'] },
    { question: '독:なく、なる、ならす/음:めい', answer: ['鳴'] },
    { question: '독:こめ/음:べい、まい', answer: ['米'] },
    { question: '독:むぎ/음:ばく', answer: ['麦'] },
    { question: '독:고기/음:にく', answer: ['肉'] },
    { question: '독:た(べる)、く(う)、くら(う)/음:しょく、[じき]', answer: ['食'] },
    { question: '독:차/음:さ、ちゃ', answer: ['茶'] },
    { question: '독:みち/음:どう、[とう]', answer: ['道'] },
    { question: '독:매양/음:まい', answer: ['毎'] },
    { question: '독:돌/음:しゅう', answer: ['週'] },
    { question: '독:あさ/음:ちょう', answer: ['朝'] },
    { question: '독:ひる/음:ちゅう', answer: ['昼'] },
    { question: '독:よ、よる/음:や', answer: ['夜'] },
    { question: '독:とき/음:じ', answer: ['時'] },
    { question: '독:빛날/음:よう', answer: ['曜'] },
    { question: '독:なか(ば)/음:はん', answer: ['半'] },
    { question: '독:서울/음:きょう、けい', answer: ['京'] },
    { question: '독:さと/음:り', answer: ['里'] },
    { question: '독:あ(う)/음:かい、え', answer: ['会'] },
    { question: '독:やしろ/음:しゃ', answer: ['社'] },
    { question: '독:おおやけ/음:こう', answer: ['公'] },
    { question: '독:その/음:えん', answer: ['園'] },
    { question: '독:てら/음:じ', answer: ['寺'] },
    { question: '독:まじ(わる)、まじ(える)、ま(じる)、ま(ざる)、ま(ぜる)、か(う)、か(わす)/음:こう', answer: ['交'] },
    { question: '독:그림/음:かい、え', answer: ['絵'] },
    { question: '독:그림/음:が、かく', answer: ['画'] },
    { question: '독:い(う)、こと/음:げん、ごん', answer: ['言'] },
    { question: '독:かた(る)、かた(らう)/음:ご', answer: ['語'] },
    { question: '독:おし(える)、おそ(わる)/음:きょう', answer: ['教'] },
    { question: '독:むろ/음:しつ', answer: ['室'] },
    { question: '독:장인/음:こう、く', answer: ['工'] },
    { question: '독:つく(る)/음:さく、さ', answer: ['作'] },
    { question: '독:はか(る)、はか(らう)/음:けい', answer: ['計'] },
    { question: '독:셈/음:さん', answer: ['算'] },
    { question: '독:점/음:てん', answer: ['点'] },
    { question: '독:かず、かぞ(える)/음:すう、[す]', answer: ['数'] },
    { question: '독:よ(む)/음:どく、とく、[とう]', answer: ['読'] },
    { question: '독:か(く)/음:しょ', answer: ['書'] },
    { question: '독:しる(す)/음:き', answer: ['記'] },
    { question: '독:あたら(しい)、あら(た)、にい/음:しん', answer: ['新'] },
    { question: '독:き(く)、き(こえる)/음:ぶん、もん', answer: ['聞'] },
    { question: '독:차례/음:ばん', answer: ['番'] },
    { question: '독:く(む)、くみ/음:そ', answer: ['組'] },
    { question: '독:うた、うた(う)/음:か', answer: ['歌'] },
    { question: '독:こえ、[こわ]/음:せい、[しょう]', answer: ['声'] },
    { question: '독:たの(しい)、たの(しむ)/음:がく、らく', answer: ['楽'] }
  ]
}
